# Teekam Chand Mandan

www.linkedin.com/in/teekam

mail.teekamchandmandan@gmail.com +91-8960009480

# Summary

I am a **full stack developer** with experience of working in health care industry, I graduated from **IIT Kanpur** with Bachelors in **Computer Science and Engineering**. Currently, I work at Circle of Life Healthcare Pvt Ltd. I am interested in solving problems, making user centric products and learning new things.

### EXPERIENCE

### Circle of Life Healthcare Pvt Ltd

New Delhi

Product Developer

Aug 2018 - Present

• **ZEVAC**: Extended the **node.js back-end** along with the **front-end vanilla JavaScript** code of Zevac, a personalised hospital antibiogram and antibiotic stewardship tool, which was demonstrated to various clients for feedback.

Developed the front-end of Zevac after tech-stack finalization, from scratch using React which was deployed at AIIMS Delhi. Worked in a team of three to make the same with added functionalities for AIIMS Rishikesh.

• ETL: Responsible for maintaining and extending the code developed by Talentica for the ETL of AIIMS Delhi data to create the staging store to be used in general for all products in COL. Talend Open Studio was used for creating the ETL jobs.

Product Intern May 2018 - Aug 2018

- SKED: Developed the front-end of SKED from scratch, the smart OPD appointment scheduler, in vanilla JavaScript. Also developed the backend in Express framework of node.js working with the data-science team. SKED was developed for AIIMS Delhi.
- ZEVAC: Responsible for maintaining and extending the front-end of the prototype version of ZEVAC.

### EDUCATION

#### Indian Institute of Technology Kanpur

Aug 2013- May 2018

Bachelors in Computer Science and Engineering

CPI: 7.4/10

### SKILLS

Languages: C, C++, Python, MATLAB, SQL, HTML, JavaScript, CSS

Libraries: React, Redux, Jest, Enzyme, d3, Puppeteer

Frameworks: Django, Express, Bootstrap

Tools: Talend Open Studio, Dbeaver, Git, LATEX

Others: Node.js, MongoDb, PostgreSQl

# SCHOLASTIC ACHIEVEMENTS

• Secured All India Rank 1244 in JEE ADVANCED out of 150,000 students.	2013
• Secured All India Rank 444 in JEE MAINS out of 1,200,000 students with a score of 317/360.	2013
• Selected for the INSPIRE Scholarship by DST Govt. of India.	2013
• Awarded the <b>certificate of merit</b> in All India Senior Secondary Certificate Examination with a	
perfect score in Mathematics $(100/100)$ .	2013
• Selected for Kishore Vaigyanik Protsahan Yojana with All India Rank 220.	2012
• Awarded the <b>certificate of merit</b> in Secondary School Examination by C.B.S.E.	2011
• Secured International Rank 47 in the 15th NSO and International rank 18 in the 6th IMO,	
organised by Science Olympiad Foundation.	2012

#### EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

• Technical Secretary, Association of Computing Activities, IIT Kanpur
--

• CADET, 2-UP CTR, National Cadet Corps, IIT Kanpur

2014 2013